

0435 174 438



Muntazhar123@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am an energetic and motivated 19 year old looking for casual work in order to obtain work experience and generate income. I'm very keen to find a position in a customer service environment to be able to use my strong interpersonal and communication skills.

Referess: Bambang Durrani UX Designer bambangdurrani@gmail.com

0413881009

SKILLS

Communication

Teamwork

Time Management

Open to change

Able to adapt

EDUCATION

School (Completed)

Islamic College Of Brisbane 2007 - 2019

Diploma of Leadership and Management (Completed)

SITS

January 2019 – November 2019

Certificate 2 in Electro technology (Completed)

*TAFE Acacia Ridge*February 2018 – November 2018

EXPERIENCE

Kitchenhand

Lord Of The Wings/ Westfield Carindale/ February 2019 - Present

Support day to day operations of the kitchen by assisting cooks, food preparation, maintaining orderliness of food supplies and equipment and sanitation control

- Clean food prep areas and storage
- Manage cold room storage
- Wash dishes

Farm Assistance

Meager Farms/ Perth/ December 2018 – February 2019

Assisted farm owner by ensuring the proper fruits were picked and farm equipment is properly maintained

- Fruit picking
- Maintain equipment
- Operate equipment

Mail Officer Christmas Casual

Australia Post Brisbane Parcel Facility- November 2020-February 2021-November 2021-January 2022

Worked with other mail officers to ensure small and large parcels going through the facility were handled safely through safe working practices and warehouse technology.